Captain! We should be in this fight.
You know that isn't an option.
Even if we join them. none of our
weapons would deal any damage.
We don't have a choice in the matter.
It's in the hands of the hunters.
Stand your ground and fight!
If they get past us.
the frontline's history!
No! This is hopeless!
Might've stood a chance if we
were higher ranked. but we're not!
Damn it. I'm... fading fast!
Healing magic?
Whoa. That worked instantly!
Hey. look out!
Duck. Now!
Go. Yoonho!
Right!
Yes. They're here.
Leave it to the S-Rank
hunters to clean house!
I think Byung-gu's
a little too eager.
I'm sorry. but the sooner I act.
the more people I heal.
Besides. I only rushed in the way I did
'cause you two were close behind.
Hm.
Huh?
It's big. but I don't think
we've made it to the boss yet.
Probably just the lead
pest of this infestation.
Byung-gu. look after the wounded.
Don't have to tell me twice.
I'm on it.
Are you ready for this. Eunseok?
You know it!
-You're a tank. Damn.
-And?
-Hm.
-Hm?
This wasn't the leader after all.
Lucky us.
Seems they made it.
No doubt in the nick of time.
Well. well. Suppose we
should get started. too.
Guild Master! On your order!
Right.
All units. attack!
More than a decade ago. a
series of pathways appeared
connecting our world
to another dimension.
And ushering in untold horrors.
For the other side of these "gates" teamed
with bizarre creatures called "magic beasts."
Though these monsters proved
immune to conventional weaponry.
some humans awakened abilities
to combat the threat.
They are known as hunters.
And the magic coursing through
them determines their rank.
There's S. A. B. C. D.
leaving E as the lowest level.
The catch is: no amount of training
will improve their power once it awakens.
A hunter's strength and rank
are set from day one.
Best of luck to you and
your crew on today's raid.
Thank you.
Hey! What's up. Mr. Kim?
Long time no see.
Now there's a face
I wasn't expecting.
Thought you said you'd had your
fill of hunting. Beom-shik.
That was before baby
number two was on the way.
A successful raid will definitely score
you a pretty nice mint for your new kiddo.
Yeah. I'm pretty nervous.
It's been a while.
So. you know. I'm super rusty.
I was always weak to begin with.
Huh? Is that a Jinwoo Sung I see?
Yo. what's going on?
Came out despite the cold. huh?
Yeah.
Nice to be working
with you guys again.
Hey. kid. have you eaten yet?
Can't fight magic beasts
running on fumes.
Right. I did eat before
I got here. thanks.
Why is everybody flagging him down?
Is that kid like a
big deal or something?
He's the exact opposite.
Jinwoo joined up
not long after you quit.
well. I call him the weakest
hunter of all mankind.
Wait. really? That's a thing?
It was once he got hospitalized
after a trip through an E-Rank gate.
If that isn't weak.
then I don't know what is.
It's hard to picture
of someone being that bad.
But he is. So just him being here
means it's gonna be a real easy raid.
Aha. Gotcha.
We should probably drop it.
I'd hate for him to overhear us.
Too late. Heard every word.
Well. they didn't say anything
that isn't true. so I can't argue.
Jinwoo! You got hurt again!
Yeah. but I'll live.
It's good to see you. Joohee.
How about you skip the small talk
and explain what happened to you?
Oh. I...
You know. the same thing
that usually happens.
You seriously need to be
more careful.
I heard you even had a hospital stay.
Hey. silver lining. though. is
that I was the only one hurt.
So what exactly went wrong?
The rest of the team was a higher-rank.
and the dungeon was an E.
so they didn't think
to bring a healer.
They didn't bring a healer?
Of all the thoughtless.
self-centered things to do!
Not like I'm mad. It isn't
their fault I'm so weak.
I'm used to being treated
that way by hunters.
-Figured you knew that.
-Hm.
It looks like they're ready
to head inside. Come on.
The name's Chiyul Song. and
unless any of you have objections.
I volunteer to be the
leader of our dungeon raid.
Speak now or hold your peace.
Nope. I'm all for it.
Chiyul is the most skilled
out of everybody here.
One less worry if he's in charge.
Working with you. sir.
is an absolute privilege.
Thanks.
Now. with that settled...
Shall we?
Hey. kid.
Hang behind the rest of the
pack and don't get yourself hurt.
Good idea. I'll try.
Focus on succeeding. not trying.
This knife has barely
any magic power in it.
but it was the only weapon
I could afford.
Hey. it's better than nothing.
All right. let's see this
through to the end.
Ah. welcome back. Chairman Go.
How was your meeting
with the administration?
We covered the usual talking points.
Dungeon breaks
are a constant problem.
but they still want the resources
we collect from every open gate.
Their demands are logical.
Anyone with sense would agree.
Hunting's now one of the most
lucrative careers on earth
thanks to the treasures
found in those monster dens.
Who would have guessed the
trophies inside magic beasts.
these essence stones.
would be so valuable?
I actually got one.
I can hardly believe it.
Jinwoo!
-You have to fight him off!
-Stay back. Joohee!
I gotta go back and help
with the main assault.
Look after him and
patch him up if you can.
Right. I will.
You're going to be okay.
I'll make you good as new.
We hunters gather essence
stones from high ranked beasts
and use them to create
weapons and armor.
That allow us to take down even
more creatures in a vicious cycle.
One would think we'd
just harvest mana crystals
since they perform
the same function.
Yet they're less potent
and make for weaker gear.
But the government's interested
in a much different use?
As a new power source. Yes.
They're safer than nuclear. More
efficient than water. wind or geothermal.
And don't pollute the
atmosphere like fossil fuels.
Quite simply. the ideal clean energy.
As we speak. scientists are working to get
those magic minerals to produce electricity.
A rare fuel source only
hunters are able to collect.
Making the burden that all hunters
bear heavier than it already was.
We did it!
I gotta hand it to you. Mr. Song.
you know how to call 'em!
Now be honest. you aren't
just staying on as a hunter
because you're too
stubborn to quit. right?
It's only a matter of when. not if.
something much worse happens.
I thought your stomach was all that
needed healing. but you're hurt everywhere!
Sorry.
I'm not asking for an
apology here. okay?
I'm worried about you.
Everyone. good?
All loot collected?
If it can fetch a price.
safe to say we got it.
Mana crystals are scarce
here as essence stones.
This dungeon was one dry cash cow.
I guess it's over.
And all I have to show for it is
a single E-Rank essence stone.
What a crap reward
for risking my life.
Hey!
Come take a look at this. guys!
-A cave?
-Or tunnel maybe?
Either way. it seems to go pretty far.
This has to be a double dungeon.
Never seen one in person. though.
I was wondering why there weren't
any signs of this place shutting down
after we beat that mutt.
I have to admit. that thought
crossed my mind. too.
Then there's more.
Maybe. this cash cow might
not be as dry as we assumed.
Listen up. ladies and gents.
Standard procedures is to report cases
like this to the Hunters Association.
And wait for their approval.
Now. hang on a second here.
That'd give other hunters a chance
to beat the boss and loot the goods.
There isn't any part of a D-Rank dungeon
that would be out of our group's league.
He's got another kid on the way.
He was banking on a
decent haul from this raid.
It'd be okay to bend
the rules a tiny bit. right?
Just a smidge?
I understand how you feel.
But going any farther
would endanger our lives.
So I say we put it to a vote.
-I'm not feeling it.
-Well. I am.
-I vote no.
-Same here.
It's worth checking out.
-I agree.
-Me too.
I-I beg to differ.
-Come on. let's go.
-We'll be fine.
I'm sorry. everyone.
I really don't want to.
All right. That's six in favor
of going and six opposed.
Which would make Jinwoo here
the deciding vote.
What. i-it's up to me?
Even if the danger isn't above a
D-Rank. I'm in trouble no matter what.
Still with Dad missing.
I'm the only one
who can provide for my family.
Mom's treatments aren't free.
And then there's
my sister's college tuition.
I don't want money. I need it.
I vote yes.
Raise your right hand. place it on
a black crystal and just try to relax.
We're ready for whoever's next.
We would love a C-Rank hunter
such as yourself to join our guild.
Just look at that bottom section
and you'll find our labor conditions
listed in extensive detail.
As of right now. a B-Rank hunter and
two C-Ranks agreed to sign with our guild.
So it's going rather well. I'd say.
I think you'll be
pleased. Guild Master.
I already am.
If anybody seems like an asset.
make them an offer
regardless of their age or gender.
I doubt they'll compare to
someone like Hae-in Cha.
but the world is full of surprises.
Purse thieves! Stop them!
Outta the damn way!
Holy!
Huh?!
Move. lady! D'you wanna die?
-Gosh. that was incredible.
-Here.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
The S-Rank hunter?
I'd like to leave.
Look at her go!
That's an S-Rank hunter for you.
How long's it been
since we started this trek?
About 40 minutes.
Gates close an hour after the boss is
defeated. so we'll have 20 minutes to spare.
Joohee. I'm really sorry.
What'd you do now?
I voted yes to come down here.
Even though you hoped
that we'd call it quits.
I'm the last thing you should
be worried about. so stop it.
I'll stop if you're sure you're okay.
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm obviously not okay.
Get a sudden case of amnesia?
Or has it not occurred to you
that goblin could've struck
a little higher and ended your life?
Healing up that wound along with
your arms and legs wasn't easy. Jinwoo!
I swear you hit your head.
That's the only explanation for
how much of an idiot you're being!
I'm sorry.
I can't deny.
Joohee's B-Rank healing spells have
come in clutch on more than one occasion.
Do you really grasp the issue here?
Yeah.
Well. in that case. you could
always show your thanks
by taking me out to eat somewhere.
Why the shock? Is the thought of
treating me to a meal so upsetting to you?
No. no. no. no. no.
That's not it at all.
Finally! We found the lair!
Rare to see an actual door
on one of these.
It's kind of unnerving.
Mm-hm.
Didn't walk that marathon
to turn back empty-handed.
No. sure as heck didn't.
The team moves forward
together. All 13 of us.
Isn't that right?
Yep. That's the deal.
For those who don't know me.
I'm Gunhee Go.
Greetings from the Hunter's
Association's current chair.
Some of you newly awakened will
choose to become hunters. Some won't.
But I ask that you consider
carefully before deciding.
It's been ten years since the gates
appeared. yet they still remain a mystery
for the most part.
So to become a hunter
is to risk your life.
Even those accustomed to raids
cannot let their guards down.
Refrain from growing
arrogant or careless.
My best advice to ensure
your survival would be:
stay both humble and afraid.
Heh. "Let there be light."
And a dope atmosphere.
This dungeon's unique all right.
What's with the old statues?
They each have something different.
Yeah. a weapon or an instrument.
Oh. whoa.
He makes the others seem like toys.
That's damn huge.
-He a king?
-King of creepiness.
So where are the mana crystals
and magic beasts?
I'm saying I don't even see bugs.
What's this for? Divination?
Mister Song!
Something's written over here.
In ancient script. of course.
"The Cartenon Temple's
Commandments are as follows."
"First. thou shalt worship God."
-"Second. thou shalt praise God."
-J-Jinwoo!
"Third. thou shalt prove thy faith."
That huge stone statue.
I saw its eyes move.
It's been watching us
this entire time.
Uh...
There's no way.
You're seeing things.
"You will not leave alive?"
The door! It just shut on its own!
-But why?
-It's fine.
I'm sure we can open it
back up again.
Better hope so.
See. this is what we get
for taking a stupid risk.
I knew we shouldn't have
kept going. but I was outvoted.
If there's treasure lying around.
you idiots are welcome to it.
I'm leaving.
Look out. it's a trap!
-Didn't stand a chance.
-They'll get us. too!
What now?
Do we fight those things?
That guy who died.
he must've been D-Rank at least.
Stronger than me. anyway.
I mean. who isn't?
And he was gone. Just like that.
What's going on?
This is a D-Rank dungeon.
No. no. there aren't supposed
to be things like that down here.
If these statues are moving.
then that means...
I've stared death in the face plenty
of times since I became a hunter.
In my first raid. I lost my
party and wound up stranded.
E-Rank monsters have
hospitalized me for weeks.
There was a time I nearly
starved to death in a labyrinth.
It could be the lowest
of low-ranked dungeons.
but I'll still be
fighting for my life.
Most hunters buy upgraded gear with the
cash they make from selling essence stones.
They take down stronger
beasts. reap bigger rewards.
But I break the bank just
splurging on cheap knives.
and once they break. that's it.
I'm back to fighting
with my bare hands.
Even my shoes are shot.
And so. day after excruciating day...
...I endure the mockery
and perform this
life-threatening job that
takes way more than it gives.
'Cause I've learned that
I can survive most anything.
if I keep my eyes
peeled for opportunities.
Maybe that's why I was able to tell.
Get down now!
What the hell?
-For real.
-How'd we trigger it?
-You think I know?
-Are you all right. Beom-shik?
Somehow. What about you?
I'm fine.
No more.
Please. no more!
What just happened?
This can't be real.
But it is. we're trapped.
Done for.
Dead.
We're all gonna die!